<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 02/26/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>SkelNetOn - CVPR 2019</title><link>http://ubee.enseeiht.fr/skelneton/challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>We release our dataset in different formats to run a competition with our workshop. We provide a shape dataset with corresponding skeleton representations in three domains, as well as some complementary sources (pre/post processing, sampling, and data augmentation scripts). The challenge will be posed as extracting the skeleton from a given shape, as detailed below. Mission 1: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21685">Shape Pixels to Skeleton Pixels</a> Mission 2: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21697">Shape Points to Skeleton Points</a> Mission 3: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21775">Parametric Skeletons</a></description></item><item><title>MolHack 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21716</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Verify your residency of <b>Taiwan</b>! At the minimum, the MolHack challenge will require the participants to build and train a Conditional Generative DNN model that can generate new small molecules such that the newly generated small molecules have similar MACCS fingerprints as the target MACCS fingerprint upon which the generation of the molecules is conditioned.</description></item><item><title>2019语言与智能技术竞赛 Language and Intelligence Challenge</title><link>http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>本届比赛设立了三个任务： 1. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/read'>机器阅读理解任务 Machine Reading Comprehension</a>：让机器阅读文本然后回答和阅读内容相关的问题， 阅读理解旨在使机器具备理解自然语言的能力。 2. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/talk'>知识驱动对话 Knowledge-driven Dialogue</a>：知识驱动对话是一种人机对话任务，机器根据知识信息构建的图谱进行主动聊天， 旨在使机器具备模拟人类用语言进行信息传递的能力。 3. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/kg'>信息抽取任务 Information Extraction</a>：信息抽取是指从自然语言文本中抽取实体、属性、关系等信息， 旨在使机器具备从海量文本自动构建知识的能力。</description></item><item><title>国际大数据分析竞赛 IEEE ISI-World Cup 2019</title><link>http://www.linkx.ac.cn/#/competition</link><category>AC</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>本次比赛基于3500家上市公司全量信息，描述公司在财务、法务、股权、经营状况、舆论等方面的属性特征，共设计两个任务， 两个任务将单独进行排名。团队可以报名一个或两个任务。 We provide full size information for over 3,500 listed companies in this competition. Two missions are given, based on the companies' attributes in terms of finance, legal affairs, equity, business status, public opinion, etc. And they will be ranked separately. One participation team can registrate one mission or two. Mission 1: 企业投资价值评估 Company Investment Value Evaluation Mission 2: 法律诉讼类型预测 Company Investment Value Evaluation</description></item><item><title>eHealth-KD @IberLEF 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21781</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>More details are available at: <a href='https://knowledge-learning.github.io/ehealthkd-2019/'>https://knowledge-learning.github.io/ehealthkd-2019</a></description></item><item><title>ICDAR 2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Scanned Receipts OCR and Information Extraction</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=13</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Scanned receipts OCR and information extraction (SROIE) play critical roles in streamlining document-intensive processes and office automation in many financial, accounting and taxation areas. </description></item><item><title>ICDAR2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Large-scale Street View Text with Partial Labeling</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=16</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>This challenge focuses on scene text reading in natural images, which can be broken down into scene text detection and spotting problems, based on the proposed Large-scale Street View Text with Partial Labeling (LSVT) dataset.</description></item><item><title>ICDAR2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Arbitrary-Shaped Text</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=14</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>This is a challenge of scene text understanding, which can be broken down into scene text detection, recognition, and spotting problems. The main novelty of this competition resides in the nature of the competition's dataset - the ArT dataset. </description></item><item><title>ICDAR 2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Reading Chinese Text on Signboard</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=12</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>We collect and construct a practical and challenging multi-orientation natural scene text dataset (TORS-25K) with 25,000 images, which consist of lots of restaurant signboards. TORS dataset includes 25,000 labeled images that are collected in the wild by phone cameras under uncontrolled conditions. It mainly focuses on Chinese text on the restaurant signboards.</description></item><item><title>ICDAR 2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Scene Text Visual Question Answering</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=11</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>The ICDAR 2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Scene Text Visual Question Answering, focuses on a specific type of Visual Question Answering task, where understanding the textual information in a scene is necessary in order to give an answer.</description></item><item><title>ICDAR 2019 Robust Reading Challenge on Multi-lingual scene text detection and recognition</title><link>http://rrc.cvc.uab.es/?ch=15</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>This new competition aims at assessing the ability of state of the art methods to detect and recognize multi-lingual text. This situation is encountered in modern cities where multiple cultures live and communicate together, where users see various scripts and languages in a way which prevent using much a priori knowledge. Multi-lingual text also poses a problem when analyzing streams of contents gathered on the Internet.</description></item></channel></rss>