<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 03/17/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>CareerCon 2019 - Help Navigate Robots</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/career-con-2019</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Compete to get your resume in front of our sponsors</description></item><item><title>中兴捧月“神算师”算法大赛</title><link>http://challenge.zte.net/suanfa.php</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/RL/SP/DM</category><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>2019 年中兴捧月神算师算法大赛（FANTASTIC ALGORITHM）是由中兴通讯面向全球大学生举办的校园赛事。 本届算法大赛分为线上初赛和线下总决赛两轮，设置四大算法方向（四大门派、七道赛题）供参赛者根据兴趣自由选择。 阿尔法·勒克斯特派：<b>深度学习模型优化加速</b> 迪杰斯特拉派：<b>网络流量均衡、报文分类格则处理</b> 图令派：<b>人工智能音频预处理</b> 傅里叶派：<b>无线信道估计、射频失真建模、智能调度算法</b></description></item><item><title>Aerial Cactus Identification</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/aerial-cactus-identification</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Determine whether an image contains a columnar cactus</description></item><item><title>CARLA Autonomous Driving Challenge</title><link>http://carlachallenge.org/challenge/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/RL</category><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The CARLA Autonomous Driving challenge encourages the development of state-of-the-art autonomous driving systems to tackle complex traffic scenarios. Track 1 - LIDAR, GPS and Cameras. All sensors track, for robotics teams that want to leverage the power of sensor fusion. Track 2 - Cameras and GPS. Only cameras track, for brave ML teams that want to explore driving with cameras. Track 3 - HD map, waypoints and all sensors. Map-based track, for teams that want to exploit available AD stacks based on HD maps and pre-computed waypoints Track 4 - Scene layout. A perception-less track, for teams that don’t want to deal with perception and prefer to focus on planning and control aspects.</description></item><item><title>Data Science for Good: CareerVillage.org</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/data-science-for-good-careervillage</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Match career advice questions with professionals in the field</description></item><item><title>2019未来杯高校AI挑战赛: 图像-发现超新星</title><link>https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/1</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>设计一个目标检测模型，从天文望远镜拍摄到的影像中发现疑似新星、超新星。</description></item><item><title>2019未来杯高校AI挑战赛: 语音-跨设备说话人识别</title><link>https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/2</link><category>PF</category><category>SP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>设计一个声纹锁，家庭成员可以在特定设备上通过任意3句短句注册身份，仅家庭成员通过说任意短句可以开锁，未注册人员（攻击者）无法通过语音开锁。</description></item><item><title>Building Educational Applications 2019 Shared Task: Grammatical Error Correction</title><link>https://www.cl.cam.ac.uk/research/nl/bea2019st/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Grammatical error correction (GEC) is the task of automatically correcting grammatical errors in text; e.g. [I follows his advices -> I followed his advice]. There are 3 tracks in the BEA 2019 shared task: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21922">Restricted Track</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21923">Unrestricted Track</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21924">Low Resource Track</a></description></item><item><title>IroSvA: Irony Detection in Spanish Variants</title><link>http://www.autoritas.net/IroSvA2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Welcome to IroSvA (Irony Detection in Spanish Variants) the first shared task fully dedicated to identify the presence of irony in short messages (tweets and news comments) written in Spanish.</description></item><item><title>NEGES 2019: Negation in Spanish</title><link>http://www.sepln.org/workshops/neges2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>this task aims to advance the study of this phenomenon in Spanish, the second most widely spoken language in the world and the third most widely used on the Internet. Sub-task A: Negation cues detection Sub-task B: Role of negation in sentiment analysis</description></item><item><title>2019 SUMO Challenge</title><link>https://sumochallenge.org/2019-sumo-challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The 2019 Scene Understanding and Modeling (SUMO) Challenge encourages the development of algorithms for complete understanding of 3D indoor scenes from 360 degree RGB-D panoramas. The target 3D models of indoor scenes include all visible layout elements and objects complete with pose, semantic information, and texture. Algorithms submitted are evaluated at 3 levels of complexity corresponding to 3 tracks of the challenge: oriented 3D bounding boxes, oriented 3D voxel grids, and oriented 3D meshes.</description></item><item><title>Named Entity Recognition and Relation Extraction for Portuguese</title><link>http://www.inf.pucrs.br/linatural/wordpress/iberlef-2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The main objective of these tasks is to propose to participants the challenge of applying their systems/solutions to the activities of Named Entity Recognition (NER) and/or Relation Extraction (RE) in Portuguese texts. Task 1: Named Entity Recognition Task 2: Relation Extraction for Named Entities Task 3: General Open Relation Extraction</description></item><item><title>MEX-A3T: Authorship and aggressiveness analysis in Twitter: case study in Mexican Spanish</title><link>https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of the second edition of MEX-A3T is to further improve the research in these two important NLP tasks as well as to continue pushing the computational treatment of the Mexican Spanish. The MEX-A3T@IberLEF2019 has the following two tracks: <a href="https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/tracks/AP?authuser=0">AUTHOR PROFILING TRACK</a> <a href="https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/tracks/AI?authuser=0">AGGRESSIVENESS DETECTION TRACK</a></description></item><item><title>TASS 2019: Sentiment Analysis Task at SEPLN</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21957</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The first aim of this task is the furtherance of research on sentiment analysis in Spanish with a special interest on the language used in Twitter. </description></item><item><title>TextVQA Challenge 2019</title><link>https://textvqa.org/challenge</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Studies have shown that a dominant class of questions asked by visually impaired users on images of their surrounding involves reading text in the image. But today’s VQA models can not read! To aid and pivot research in the direction of VQA models with the capability to read, we introduce a new dataset TextVQA. TextVQA which requires model to read text from images and reason over it to answer questions about an image.</description></item><item><title>HAHA 2019: Humor Analysis based on Human Annotation</title><link>https://www.fing.edu.uy/inco/grupos/pln/haha/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The HAHA evaluation campaign proposes different subtasks related to automatic humor detection. In order to carry out the tasks, an annotated corpus of tweets in Spanish will be provided.</description></item><item><title>FACT: Factuality Analysis and Classification Task</title><link>https://www.fing.edu.uy/inco/grupos/pln/fact/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this task is the determination of the status of verb events with respect to factuality in Spanish texts.</description></item><item><title>WebVision Challenge 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21721</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this challenge is to advance the area of learning knowledge and representation from web data. The web data not only contains huge numbers of visual images, but also rich meta information concerning these visual data, which could be exploited to learn good representations and models. In 2019, we organize one track for this challenge: WebVision Image Classification Task.</description></item><item><title>KiTS19 Challenge</title><link>https://kits19.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this challenge is to accelerate the development of reliable kidney and kidney tumor semantic segmentation methodologies. </description></item></channel></rss>