<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 03/12/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>2019未来杯高校AI挑战赛: 图像-发现超新星</title><link>https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/1</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>设计一个目标检测模型，从天文望远镜拍摄到的影像中发现疑似新星、超新星。</description></item><item><title>2019未来杯高校AI挑战赛: 语音-跨设备说话人识别</title><link>https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/2</link><category>PF</category><category>SP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>设计一个声纹锁，家庭成员可以在特定设备上通过任意3句短句注册身份，仅家庭成员通过说任意短句可以开锁，未注册人员（攻击者）无法通过语音开锁。</description></item><item><title>Building Educational Applications 2019 Shared Task: Grammatical Error Correction</title><link>https://www.cl.cam.ac.uk/research/nl/bea2019st/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Grammatical error correction (GEC) is the task of automatically correcting grammatical errors in text; e.g. [I follows his advices -> I followed his advice]. There are 3 tracks in the BEA 2019 shared task: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21922">Restricted Track</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21923">Unrestricted Track</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21924">Low Resource Track</a></description></item><item><title>IroSvA: Irony Detection in Spanish Variants</title><link>http://www.autoritas.net/IroSvA2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Welcome to IroSvA (Irony Detection in Spanish Variants) the first shared task fully dedicated to identify the presence of irony in short messages (tweets and news comments) written in Spanish.</description></item><item><title>NEGES 2019: Negation in Spanish</title><link>http://www.sepln.org/workshops/neges2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>this task aims to advance the study of this phenomenon in Spanish, the second most widely spoken language in the world and the third most widely used on the Internet. Sub-task A: Negation cues detection Sub-task B: Role of negation in sentiment analysis</description></item><item><title>2019 SUMO Challenge</title><link>https://sumochallenge.org/2019-sumo-challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The 2019 Scene Understanding and Modeling (SUMO) Challenge encourages the development of algorithms for complete understanding of 3D indoor scenes from 360 degree RGB-D panoramas. The target 3D models of indoor scenes include all visible layout elements and objects complete with pose, semantic information, and texture. Algorithms submitted are evaluated at 3 levels of complexity corresponding to 3 tracks of the challenge: oriented 3D bounding boxes, oriented 3D voxel grids, and oriented 3D meshes.</description></item><item><title>Named Entity Recognition and Relation Extraction for Portuguese</title><link>http://www.inf.pucrs.br/linatural/wordpress/iberlef-2019/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The main objective of these tasks is to propose to participants the challenge of applying their systems/solutions to the activities of Named Entity Recognition (NER) and/or Relation Extraction (RE) in Portuguese texts. Task 1: Named Entity Recognition Task 2: Relation Extraction for Named Entities Task 3: General Open Relation Extraction</description></item><item><title>MEX-A3T: Authorship and aggressiveness analysis in Twitter: case study in Mexican Spanish</title><link>https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of the second edition of MEX-A3T is to further improve the research in these two important NLP tasks as well as to continue pushing the computational treatment of the Mexican Spanish. The MEX-A3T@IberLEF2019 has the following two tracks: <a href="https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/tracks/AP?authuser=0">AUTHOR PROFILING TRACK</a> <a href="https://sites.google.com/view/mex-a3t/tracks/AI?authuser=0">AGGRESSIVENESS DETECTION TRACK</a></description></item><item><title>TASS 2019: Sentiment Analysis Task at SEPLN</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21957</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The first aim of this task is the furtherance of research on sentiment analysis in Spanish with a special interest on the language used in Twitter. </description></item><item><title>TextVQA Challenge 2019</title><link>https://textvqa.org/challenge</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>Studies have shown that a dominant class of questions asked by visually impaired users on images of their surrounding involves reading text in the image. But today’s VQA models can not read! To aid and pivot research in the direction of VQA models with the capability to read, we introduce a new dataset TextVQA. TextVQA which requires model to read text from images and reason over it to answer questions about an image.</description></item><item><title>HAHA 2019: Humor Analysis based on Human Annotation</title><link>https://www.fing.edu.uy/inco/grupos/pln/haha/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The HAHA evaluation campaign proposes different subtasks related to automatic humor detection. In order to carry out the tasks, an annotated corpus of tweets in Spanish will be provided.</description></item><item><title>FACT: Factuality Analysis and Classification Task</title><link>https://www.fing.edu.uy/inco/grupos/pln/fact/</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this task is the determination of the status of verb events with respect to factuality in Spanish texts.</description></item><item><title>WebVision Challenge 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21721</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this challenge is to advance the area of learning knowledge and representation from web data. The web data not only contains huge numbers of visual images, but also rich meta information concerning these visual data, which could be exploited to learn good representations and models. In 2019, we organize one track for this challenge: WebVision Image Classification Task.</description></item><item><title>KiTS19 Challenge</title><link>https://kits19.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of this challenge is to accelerate the development of reliable kidney and kidney tumor semantic segmentation methodologies. </description></item><item><title>Explorer Challenge: A $1million prize pool to find Australia’s next big mineral deposit</title><link>https://unearthed.solutions/u/competitions/explorer-challenge</link><category>PF</category><category>DM/CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Join a global challenge to test the limits of data science and geology and develop new ideas about mineral exploration. OZ Minerals, a modern mining company, is opening up >2TB of their own private data from their exploration project, Mount Woods. Can you use this data to predict the next mineral deposit in South Australia? The winning models will be tested in real life, the top predictions will be drilled in 2019.</description></item><item><title>首届中国心电智能大赛</title><link>http://mdi.ids.tsinghua.edu.cn/</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/SP</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>自2012年起，国家陆续出台政策推动健康医疗和大数据的融合发展，从“健康中国”战略到“两个一百年”奋斗目标，健康医疗大数据已成为国家战略的创新需要，是国家及民族复兴所需的核心技术及国之重器。在此背景下，由清华大学临床医学院和数据科学研究院以及多家重点医院联合主办的首届中国心电智能大赛应运而生并于2018年12月20日正式启动。此次大赛获得天津市卫健委和河北省卫健委领导高度重视。预计大赛总奖金将高达百万元。</description></item><item><title>2019 Future Food Challenge</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231705/introduction?spm=5176.12281949.0.0.7e9276d8mqVJ8x</link><category>PF</category><category>DM/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Use the training data set to develop an <b>unsupervised</b> algorithm which identifies news items in the test set relating to the same food safety incident and assigns the same Event-ID to such group. </description></item></channel></rss>