<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 06/03/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>2019 EE331 - Colorization</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23046</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Our goal is to make colorization from input images. The normal images are composed of RGB values, but we can represent these images into LAB values. In here, L means lightness. We cannot know the color of the image without the A and B values.</description></item><item><title>PharmaCoNER: Pharmacological Substances, Compounds and proteins and Named Entity Recognition track</title><link>http://temu.bsc.es/pharmaconer/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>For this task we have prepared a manually classified collection of clinical case sections derived from Open access Spanish medical publications, named the Spanish Clinical Case Corpus (SPACCC). The corpus contains a total of 1000 clinical cases / 396,988 words. It is noteworthy to say that this kind of narrative shows properties of both, the biomedical and medical literature as well as clinical records. Track 1: NER offset and entity classification. Track 2: Concept indexing.</description></item><item><title>政府治理大数据应用算法大赛</title><link>http://campus.chinahr.com/pages/cetctwo/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>国内外全日制<b>在校</b>大学生（包括全日制本科、硕士、博士研究生等非2019届毕业生），热爱算法建模、热爱数据分析、热爱应用开发等均可参赛。 本轮赛事仅设1题: <b>政策公文中的语义搜索</b>(需要根据输入的问题，返回对应的政策内容，以及相应的公文名称和具体条例)</description></item><item><title>DeepFashion2 Challenge 2019</title><link>https://sites.google.com/view/cvcreative/deepfashion2?authuser=0</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>DeepFashion2 (<a href="https://github.com/switchablenorms/DeepFashion2">github</a>) is a comprehensive fashion dataset. It contains 491K diverse images of 13 popular clothing categories from both commercial shopping stores and consumers. It totally has 801K clothing clothing items, where each item in an image is labeled with scale, occlusion, zoom-in, viewpoint, category, style, bounding box, dense landmarks and per-pixel mask.There are also 873K Commercial-Consumer clothes pairs. The dataset is split into a training set (391K images), a validation set (34k images), and a test set (67k images). <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23095">Track 1 Clothes Landmark Estimation</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23098">Track 2 Clothes Retrieval</a></description></item><item><title>第三届"长风杯"大数据分析与挖掘竞赛</title><link>http://contest.cfdsj.cn/index/care</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>第三届“长风杯”大数据分析与挖掘竞赛是一场面向全国普通高等院校经济与管理类、信息技术类等专业在校大学生的全国性赛事。 长风大数据平台将向本次竞赛的参赛者免费开放物流、电商、交通、公共、贸易等多行业的海量数据资源；其他生产型/服务型企业所提供真实数据。</description></item><item><title>Challenges and Opportunities in Automated Coding of COntentious Political Events (Cope 2019) @Euro CSS 2019</title><link>https://emw.ku.edu.tr/?event=challenges-and-opportunities-in-automated-coding-of-contentious-political-events</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>We use English online news archives from India and China as data sources to create the training and test corpora. India and China are the source and the target countries respectively in our setting.</description></item><item><title>Predicting Molecular Properties</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/champs-scalar-coupling</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Can you measure the magnetic interactions between a pair of atoms?</description></item><item><title>Alchemy Contest</title><link>https://alchemy.tencent.com</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The Tencent Quantum Lab has recently introduced a new molecular dataset, called Alchemy, to facilitate the development of new machine learning models useful for chemistry and materials science. The dataset lists 12 quantum mechanical properties of 130,000+ organic molecules comprising up to 12 heavy atoms (C, N, O, S, F and Cl), sampled from the <a href="http://gdb.unibe.ch/downloads/">GDBMedChem</a> database. These properties have been calculated using the open-source computational chemistry program Python-based Simulation of Chemistry Framework (<a href="https://github.com/pyscf/pyscf">PySCF</a>).</description></item><item><title>MicroNet Challenge @NeurIPS 2019</title><link>https://micronet-challenge.github.io/</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The competition consists of three different tasks. Contestants are free to submit entries for one, two, or all three tasks. Contestants are allowed to enter up to three models for each task, but will be ranked according to their top entry in each task. Entries can only be trained on the training data for the task they are entered in. No pre-training, or use of auxiliary data is allowed. <a href="http://image-net.org/index">ImageNet Classification</a>: The de facto standard dataset for image classification. The dataset is composed of 1,281,167 training images and 50,000 development images. Entries are required to achieve 75% top-1 accuracy on the public test set. <a href="https://www.cs.toronto.edu/~kriz/cifar.html">CIFAR-100 Classification</a>: A widely popular image classification dataset of small images. The dataset is composed of 50,000 training images and 10,000 development images. Entries are required to achieve 80% top-1 accuracy on the test set. <a href="https://blog.einstein.ai/the-wikitext-long-term-dependency-language-modeling-dataset/">WikiText-103 Language Modeling</a>: A language modeling dataset that emphasizes long-term dependencies. Entries will perform the standard language modeling task, predicting the next token from the current one. The dataset is composed of 103 million training words, 217 thousand development words, and 245 thousand testing words. Entries should use the standard word-level vocabulary of 267,735 tokens. Entries are required to achieve a word-level perplexity below 35 on the test set.</description></item><item><title>转子部件脱落故障预测 (Prognosis of Rotor Parts Fly-off)</title><link>http://www.industrial-bigdata.com/competition/competitionAction!showDetail2019.action?competition.competitionId=5</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>第三届工业大数据创新竞赛</b> Background: For large rotating machines, due to the high rotating speed and tremendous momentum of the rotor, the centrifugal force may lead to the loose or flying apart of the rotor parts, which brings a great threat to the operation safety of the equipment. This type of fault could lead to high maintenance cost and significant economic loss. The capture of the early symptom of rotor faults is relatively difficult and has become a worldwide challenge in the field of prognostics. It will bring significant safety value and economic benefits if the big data-based methods can detect and predict incipient faults. 赛事简要：大型旋转机组设备高速旋转、动能巨大，转子部件脱落故障给设备安全运行带来巨大威胁。而且这类故障维修成本高、耗时长，早期征兆难以捕捉，是故障预测的世界性难题。如果能通过大数据方法，实现此故障征兆的早期发现和程度预测，将带来显著的安全价值和经济效益。</description></item><item><title>第四届魔镜杯大赛</title><link>https://ai.ppdai.com/mirror/goToMirrorDetail?mirrorId=17</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description>本次比赛以互联网金融信贷业务为背景，参赛选手需要利用提供的数据，预测资产组合在未来一段时间内每日的回款金额。赛题涵盖了信贷违约预测、现金流预测等金融领域常见问题，同时又是复杂的时序问题和多目标预测问题。</description></item><item><title>The 2nd China (Hengqin) International University Quantitative Finance Competition</title><link>http://qfc-c.com</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description>第二届中国（横琴）国际高校量化金融大赛 <b>参赛要求</b> 参赛者应根据题目要求，完成一篇包括量化金融策略原理、模型的假设、建立和求解、计算方法的设计、分析和检验、模型的改进等方面的书面报告（即答卷）；并在规定竞赛期间内，将参赛策略的市场运行进行模拟仿真竞赛。根据参赛策略的测试结果（包括样本内和样本外）的收益水平及市场风险防范的效果等统一指标打分评比，以市场的标准来决定优劣，评价策略的回测和实盘模拟表现，同时考虑策略逻辑的稳健性和创新性。竞赛评奖以策略的合理性、建模的创新性、测试策略的市场适应性及收益风险水平等结果为主要标准。 <b>Requirements</b> Participants should write a report covering quantitative financial strategy theories 1) Model theoretical hypothesis and description of quantitive model 2) Data analysis 3) Strategy back testing results and performance analysis. According to the requirements of the competition, participants’ strategies will be back tested and paper traded during the required period. Evaluation and scoring will base on unified measurements including return, volatility, max drawdown of the strategies and so on. The determination of merits and evaluation of strategy back test and paper trading performance will be made according to market standards, while the robustness and innovation of the strategic logic will also be taken into consideration. Key criteria will include the rationality of the strategy, the creativeness of the model, the market adaptability of the testing strategy and the level of return and risk.</description></item></channel></rss>