<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 05/24/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>Instant Gratification</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/instant-gratification</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>A synchronous Kernels-only competition</description></item><item><title>CMRC 2019: The Third Evaluation Workshop on Chinese Machine Reading Comprehension</title><link>https://hfl-rc.github.io/cmrc2019/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>第三届“讯飞杯”中文机器阅读理解（CMRC 2019）</b>的任务是句子级填空型阅读理解（Sentence Cloze-Style Machine Reading Comprehension, SC-MRC）。 根据给定的一个叙事篇章以及若干个从篇章中抽取出的句子，参赛者需要建立模型将候选句子精准的填回原篇章中，使之成为完整的一篇文章。本任务需要机器能够根据上下文的逻辑关系判断空缺部分的内容，进一步提升了机器阅读理解的难度。</description></item><item><title>eBay SIGIR 2019 eCommerce Search Challenge: High Accuracy Recall Task</title><link>https://sigir-ecom.github.io/data-task.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/DM/NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>The challenge data consists of a set of popular search queries and a fair size set of candidate documents. Challenge participants make a boolean relevant-or-not decision for each query-document pair. Human judgments are used to create labeled training and evaluation data for a subset of the query-document pairs. Evaluation of submissions will be based on the traditional F1 metric, incorporating components of both recall and precision.</description></item><item><title>iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛</title><link>http://challenge.xfyun.cn/2019/</link><category>PF</category><category>SP/DM/CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>"iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛"是由科大讯飞发起的顶尖人工智能竞赛平台，汇聚产学研各界力量，面向全球开发者发起数据算法及创新应用类挑战，推动人工智能前沿科学研究和创新成果转化，培育人工智能产业人才，助力人工智能生态建设。 2019 年，第二届 iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛将继续开放科大讯飞优质大数据资源及人工智能核心技术，面向全球开发者发起数据算法及创新应用类挑战。 <b>阿尔茨海默综合症预测挑战赛</b>: 基于老年人在特定图片描述任务中产生的语音，给定语音数据中提取出的声学特征、主被试对话的切分信息、人工文本转写结果以及对应的认知标签，建立2分类模型预测认知标签（正常或认知障碍）。 <b>移动广告反欺诈算法挑战赛</b>: 移动广告反欺诈需要强大的数据作为支撑，本次大赛提供了讯飞AI营销云海量的现网流量数据作为训练样本，参赛选手需基于提供的样本构建模型，预测流量作弊与否。 <b>大数据应用分类标注挑战赛</b>: 选手基于提供的应用二级分类标签以及若干随机应用标注样本，实现应用分类标注算法（每个应用一个标签，以应用最主要属性对应的标签为该应用的标签）。 <b>工程机械核心部件寿命预测挑战赛</b>: 由中科云谷科技有限公司提供某类工程机械设备的核心耗损性部件的工作数据，包括部件工作时长、转速、温度、电压、电流等多类工况数据。希望参赛者利用大数据分析、机器学习、深度学习等方法，提取合适的特征、建立合适的寿命预测模型，预测核心耗损性部件的剩余寿命。</description></item><item><title>Exoplanet imaging data challenge</title><link>https://exoplanet-imaging-challenge.github.io</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>This competition is composed of two sub-challenges focusing on the two most widely used observing techniques: <b>pupil tracking</b> (angular differential imaging, ADI) and <b>multi-spectral imaging combined with pupil tracking</b> (multi-channel spectral differential imaging, ADI+mSDI).</description></item><item><title>Peking University International Competition on Ocular Disease Intelligent Recognition (ODIR-2019)</title><link>https://odir2019.grand-challenge.org/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>北京大学'智慧之眼'国际眼科疾病智能识别竞赛</b> The SG will provide participants with 5,000 structured desensitized ophthalmologic image set of patient's age, sex, binocular color fundus photos and doctors' diagnostic report. 上工医信将为参赛者提供5000组包含患者的性别、年龄、双眼彩色眼底照片和医生印象报告等的结构化脱敏后眼科的数据集。 The purpose of this challenge is to compare approaches of ophthalmic disease classification in color fundus images. Participant will have to submit classification results of eight categories for all the testing data. For every category, a classification probability (value from 0.0 to 1.0) denotes risk of a patient diagnosed with corresponding category. 该竞赛的目的是比较基于彩色眼底图像进行眼科疾病分类的不同方法。 参与者必须提交所有测试数据集的八个类别的分类结果。 对于每个类别，分类概率（值从0.0到1.0）表示患者被诊断为具有相应类别的可能性/风险。</description></item><item><title>Endoscopic Vision Challenge 2019</title><link>https://endovis.grand-challenge.org/Endoscopic_Vision_Challenge/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>As a vision CAI challenge at MICCAI, our aim is to provide a formal framework for evaluating the current state of the art, gather researchers in the field and provide high quality data with protocols for validating endoscopic vision algorithms. EndoVis 2019 Sub-challenges: <a href="https://endovissub-workflowandskill.grand-challenge.org">Surgical Workflow and Skill Analysis</a> <a href="https://endovissub2019-scared.grand-challenge.org">Stereo Correspondence and Reconstruction of Endoscopic Data</a></description></item><item><title>Mobile age group classification</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/22946</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>This is an EE331 competition leaderboard for Mobile age group classification. It consists of 157K datasamples with 85 various features and age group label (ranging from 1 to 6). The data is splitted into train : validation : test sset with 70 : 20 : 10 ratio.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Pitching Simulator</title><link>https://fastballs.wordpress.com/category/pitchfx-glossary/</link><category>PF</category><category>RL/CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>Perfect Pitching Simulator!</description></item><item><title>The Large Scale Vertebrae Segmentation Challenge (VerSe2019) </title><link>https://verse2019.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>Spine or vertebral segmentation is a crucial step in all applications regarding automated quantification of spinal morphology and pathology. With the advent of deep learning, for such a task on computed tomography (CT) scans, a big and varied data is a primary sought-after resource. Task 1: Vertebra Labelling Task 2: Vertebra Segmentation</description></item><item><title>TinyMind人民币面值&amp;冠字号编码识别挑战赛</title><link>https://www.tinymind.cn/competitions/47</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019</pubDate><description>针对人民币纸币面额及编码识别技术的深入研究，TinyMind发起本期挑战赛，诚邀广大AI界大佬,疯狂炫技，踊跃报名。 第一阶段：热身赛—— ⼈⺠币⾯值识别 第二阶段：正式赛——人民币冠字号编码识别</description></item><item><title>2019中国‘法研杯’司法人工智能挑战赛（CAIL2019）</title><link>http://cail.cipsc.org.cn</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019</pubDate><description>本次挑战赛聚焦在<b>法律要素抽取</b>、<b>法律阅读理解</b>、<b>相似案例匹配</b>三个真实场景的任务，提供海量的已标注的法律文书数据，旨在为研究者提供学术交流平台，推动语言理解和人工智能领域技术在法律领域的应用，促进法律人工智能事业的发展。今年预计于10月在北京举办颁奖会和技术研讨会。诚邀学术界和工业界的研究者和开发者积极参与，比赛中发现的重大基础性问题，在国家自然科学基金专项资金中将予以重点考虑！</description></item></channel></rss>