<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 05/30/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>转子部件脱落故障预测 (Prognosis of Rotor Parts Fly-off)</title><link>http://www.industrial-bigdata.com/competition/competitionAction!showDetail2019.action?competition.competitionId=5</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>第三届工业大数据创新竞赛</b> Background: For large rotating machines, due to the high rotating speed and tremendous momentum of the rotor, the centrifugal force may lead to the loose or flying apart of the rotor parts, which brings a great threat to the operation safety of the equipment. This type of fault could lead to high maintenance cost and significant economic loss. The capture of the early symptom of rotor faults is relatively difficult and has become a worldwide challenge in the field of prognostics. It will bring significant safety value and economic benefits if the big data-based methods can detect and predict incipient faults. 赛事简要：大型旋转机组设备高速旋转、动能巨大，转子部件脱落故障给设备安全运行带来巨大威胁。而且这类故障维修成本高、耗时长，早期征兆难以捕捉，是故障预测的世界性难题。如果能通过大数据方法，实现此故障征兆的早期发现和程度预测，将带来显著的安全价值和经济效益。</description></item><item><title>第四届魔镜杯大赛</title><link>https://ai.ppdai.com/mirror/goToMirrorDetail?mirrorId=17</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description>本次比赛以互联网金融信贷业务为背景，参赛选手需要利用提供的数据，预测资产组合在未来一段时间内每日的回款金额。赛题涵盖了信贷违约预测、现金流预测等金融领域常见问题，同时又是复杂的时序问题和多目标预测问题。</description></item><item><title>The 2nd China (Hengqin) International University Quantitative Finance Competition</title><link>http://qfc-c.com</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019</pubDate><description>第二届中国（横琴）国际高校量化金融大赛 <b>参赛要求</b> 参赛者应根据题目要求，完成一篇包括量化金融策略原理、模型的假设、建立和求解、计算方法的设计、分析和检验、模型的改进等方面的书面报告（即答卷）；并在规定竞赛期间内，将参赛策略的市场运行进行模拟仿真竞赛。根据参赛策略的测试结果（包括样本内和样本外）的收益水平及市场风险防范的效果等统一指标打分评比，以市场的标准来决定优劣，评价策略的回测和实盘模拟表现，同时考虑策略逻辑的稳健性和创新性。竞赛评奖以策略的合理性、建模的创新性、测试策略的市场适应性及收益风险水平等结果为主要标准。 <b>Requirements</b> Participants should write a report covering quantitative financial strategy theories 1) Model theoretical hypothesis and description of quantitive model 2) Data analysis 3) Strategy back testing results and performance analysis. According to the requirements of the competition, participants’ strategies will be back tested and paper traded during the required period. Evaluation and scoring will base on unified measurements including return, volatility, max drawdown of the strategies and so on. The determination of merits and evaluation of strategy back test and paper trading performance will be made according to market standards, while the robustness and innovation of the strategic logic will also be taken into consideration. Key criteria will include the rationality of the strategy, the creativeness of the model, the market adaptability of the testing strategy and the level of return and risk.</description></item><item><title>Instant Gratification</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/instant-gratification</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>A synchronous Kernels-only competition</description></item><item><title>CMRC 2019: The Third Evaluation Workshop on Chinese Machine Reading Comprehension</title><link>https://hfl-rc.github.io/cmrc2019/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>第三届“讯飞杯”中文机器阅读理解（CMRC 2019）</b>的任务是句子级填空型阅读理解（Sentence Cloze-Style Machine Reading Comprehension, SC-MRC）。 根据给定的一个叙事篇章以及若干个从篇章中抽取出的句子，参赛者需要建立模型将候选句子精准的填回原篇章中，使之成为完整的一篇文章。本任务需要机器能够根据上下文的逻辑关系判断空缺部分的内容，进一步提升了机器阅读理解的难度。</description></item><item><title>eBay SIGIR 2019 eCommerce Search Challenge: High Accuracy Recall Task</title><link>https://sigir-ecom.github.io/data-task.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/DM/NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>The challenge data consists of a set of popular search queries and a fair size set of candidate documents. Challenge participants make a boolean relevant-or-not decision for each query-document pair. Human judgments are used to create labeled training and evaluation data for a subset of the query-document pairs. Evaluation of submissions will be based on the traditional F1 metric, incorporating components of both recall and precision.</description></item><item><title>iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛</title><link>http://challenge.xfyun.cn/2019/</link><category>PF</category><category>SP/DM/CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>"iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛"是由科大讯飞发起的顶尖人工智能竞赛平台，汇聚产学研各界力量，面向全球开发者发起数据算法及创新应用类挑战，推动人工智能前沿科学研究和创新成果转化，培育人工智能产业人才，助力人工智能生态建设。 2019 年，第二届 iFLYTEK AI 开发者大赛将继续开放科大讯飞优质大数据资源及人工智能核心技术，面向全球开发者发起数据算法及创新应用类挑战。 <b>阿尔茨海默综合症预测挑战赛</b>: 基于老年人在特定图片描述任务中产生的语音，给定语音数据中提取出的声学特征、主被试对话的切分信息、人工文本转写结果以及对应的认知标签，建立2分类模型预测认知标签（正常或认知障碍）。 <b>移动广告反欺诈算法挑战赛</b>: 移动广告反欺诈需要强大的数据作为支撑，本次大赛提供了讯飞AI营销云海量的现网流量数据作为训练样本，参赛选手需基于提供的样本构建模型，预测流量作弊与否。 <b>大数据应用分类标注挑战赛</b>: 选手基于提供的应用二级分类标签以及若干随机应用标注样本，实现应用分类标注算法（每个应用一个标签，以应用最主要属性对应的标签为该应用的标签）。 <b>工程机械核心部件寿命预测挑战赛</b>: 由中科云谷科技有限公司提供某类工程机械设备的核心耗损性部件的工作数据，包括部件工作时长、转速、温度、电压、电流等多类工况数据。希望参赛者利用大数据分析、机器学习、深度学习等方法，提取合适的特征、建立合适的寿命预测模型，预测核心耗损性部件的剩余寿命。</description></item><item><title>Exoplanet imaging data challenge</title><link>https://exoplanet-imaging-challenge.github.io</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>This competition is composed of two sub-challenges focusing on the two most widely used observing techniques: <b>pupil tracking</b> (angular differential imaging, ADI) and <b>multi-spectral imaging combined with pupil tracking</b> (multi-channel spectral differential imaging, ADI+mSDI).</description></item><item><title>Peking University International Competition on Ocular Disease Intelligent Recognition (ODIR-2019)</title><link>https://odir2019.grand-challenge.org/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>北京大学'智慧之眼'国际眼科疾病智能识别竞赛</b> The SG will provide participants with 5,000 structured desensitized ophthalmologic image set of patient's age, sex, binocular color fundus photos and doctors' diagnostic report. 上工医信将为参赛者提供5000组包含患者的性别、年龄、双眼彩色眼底照片和医生印象报告等的结构化脱敏后眼科的数据集。 The purpose of this challenge is to compare approaches of ophthalmic disease classification in color fundus images. Participant will have to submit classification results of eight categories for all the testing data. For every category, a classification probability (value from 0.0 to 1.0) denotes risk of a patient diagnosed with corresponding category. 该竞赛的目的是比较基于彩色眼底图像进行眼科疾病分类的不同方法。 参与者必须提交所有测试数据集的八个类别的分类结果。 对于每个类别，分类概率（值从0.0到1.0）表示患者被诊断为具有相应类别的可能性/风险。</description></item><item><title>Endoscopic Vision Challenge 2019</title><link>https://endovis.grand-challenge.org/Endoscopic_Vision_Challenge/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>As a vision CAI challenge at MICCAI, our aim is to provide a formal framework for evaluating the current state of the art, gather researchers in the field and provide high quality data with protocols for validating endoscopic vision algorithms. EndoVis 2019 Sub-challenges: <a href="https://endovissub-workflowandskill.grand-challenge.org">Surgical Workflow and Skill Analysis</a> <a href="https://endovissub2019-scared.grand-challenge.org">Stereo Correspondence and Reconstruction of Endoscopic Data</a></description></item><item><title>Mobile age group classification</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/22946</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>This is an EE331 competition leaderboard for Mobile age group classification. It consists of 157K datasamples with 85 various features and age group label (ranging from 1 to 6). The data is splitted into train : validation : test sset with 70 : 20 : 10 ratio.</description></item><item><title>Perfect Pitching Simulator</title><link>https://fastballs.wordpress.com/category/pitchfx-glossary/</link><category>PF</category><category>RL/CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>Perfect Pitching Simulator!</description></item><item><title>The Large Scale Vertebrae Segmentation Challenge (VerSe2019) </title><link>https://verse2019.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019</pubDate><description>Spine or vertebral segmentation is a crucial step in all applications regarding automated quantification of spinal morphology and pathology. With the advent of deep learning, for such a task on computed tomography (CT) scans, a big and varied data is a primary sought-after resource. Task 1: Vertebra Labelling Task 2: Vertebra Segmentation</description></item></channel></rss>