<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 06/27/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>AI Drug Discovery: Pharmacokinetic Parameter Prediction</title><link>https://signate.jp/competitions/168</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Predict pharmacokinetic parameters from compound information and experimental data in the screening test.</description></item><item><title>第五届中间件性能挑战赛</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231714/</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>初赛：《自适应负载均衡的设计实现》复赛：《实现一个进程内基于队列的消息持久化存储引擎》</description></item><item><title>全球数据智能大赛(2019)——“数字人体”赛场一：肺部CT多病种智能诊断</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231724/</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>赛场一“数字人体”挑战赛以肺部CT多病种智能诊断为课题，开放高质量CT标注数据，要求选手提出并综合运用目标检测、深度学习等人工智能算法，识别肺结节、索条（条索状影）、动脉硬化或钙化、淋巴结钙化等多个病种，避免同一部位单病种的反复筛查，提高检测的速度和精度，辅助医生进行诊断。</description></item><item><title>CIKM 2019 EComm AI</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231719/</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description> <a href="https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231719">Predicting User Behavior Diversities in A Dynamic Interactive Environment</a> <a href="https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231721">Efficient and Novel Item Retrieval for Large-scale Online Shopping Recommendation</a></description></item><item><title>AI开发者大赛</title><link>https://www.dcjingsai.com/</link><category>PF</category><category>DM/SP/CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description> <a href="https://www.dcjingsai.com/common/cmpt/AI开发者大赛-工程机械核心部件寿命预测挑战赛_竞赛信息.html">AI开发者大赛-工程机械核心部件寿命预测挑战赛</a> <a href="https://www.dcjingsai.com/common/cmpt/AI开发者大赛-大数据应用分类标注挑战赛_竞赛信息.html">AI开发者大赛-大数据应用分类标注挑战赛</a> <a href="https://www.dcjingsai.com/common/cmpt/AI开发者大赛-广告营销反作弊算法挑战赛_竞赛信息.html">AI开发者大赛-广告营销反作弊算法挑战赛</a> <a href="https://www.pkbigdata.com/common/cmpt/AI开发者大赛-阿尔茨海默综合征预测挑战赛_竞赛信息.html">AI开发者大赛-阿尔茨海默综合征预测挑战赛</a></description></item><item><title>SIIM-ACR Pneumothorax Segmentation</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/siim-acr-pneumothorax-segmentation</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Identify Pneumothorax disease in chest x-rays</description></item><item><title>成语阅读理解大赛</title><link>https://www.biendata.com/competition/idiom/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>本次竞赛将基于选词填空的任务形式，提供大规模的成语填空训练语料。在给定若干段文本下，选手需要在提供的候选项中，依次选出填入文本中的空格处最恰当的成语。</description></item><item><title>YouCook2-BoundingBoxes Video Object Grounding Task</title><link>http://youcook2.eecs.umich.edu</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>YouCook2 is the largest task-oriented, instructional video dataset in the vision community. It contains 2000 long untrimmed videos from 89 cooking recipes; on average, each distinct recipe has 22 videos. The procedure steps for each video are annotated with temporal boundaries and described by imperative English sentences (see the example below). </description></item><item><title>Evergreen: Automatically detect drill core tray outlines in core photography</title><link>https://unearthed.solutions/u/competitions/evergreen/get-2-the-core</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>This global online competition invites innovators from around the world to build an algorithm that can determine and map the spatial extents of the core tray and then the individual rows contained within.  </description></item><item><title>Evergreen: Identify depth measurements in core images</title><link>https://unearthed.solutions/u/competitions/evergreen/get-2-core-ii-revenge-depths</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>This is an online competition inviting companies and individuals from around the world to provide a solution that can correctly identify recorded depths within a core photograph.  </description></item><item><title>Evergreen: Reduce water usage in gold processing through tailings density prediction</title><link>https://unearthed.solutions/u/competitions/evergreen/hydrosaver</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>This global online competition invites data scientists and innovators from around the world to develop a prediction model for tailings density (and therefore water consumption) in Newcrest's gold processing operations.</description></item><item><title>SMP - ECISA “拓尔思杯”中文隐式情感分析评测 2019</title><link>https://biendata.com/competition/smpecisa2019/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>欢迎来到SMP2019“拓尔思杯”中文隐式情感分析评测（The Evaluation of Chinese Implicit Sentiment Analysis，SMP-ECISA 2019）。 我们将隐式情感定义为：“不含有显式情感词，但表达了主观情感的语言片段”，并将其划分为事实型隐式情感和修辞型隐式情感。其中，修辞型隐式情感又可细分为隐喻/比喻型、反问型以及反讽型。本次评测任务中，仅针对隐式情感的识别与情感倾向性分类。</description></item><item><title>MLCAS 2019 - Sorghum head detection</title><link>https://www.register.extension.iastate.edu/mlcas2019/competition</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>This challenge uses RGB image frames of Sorghum heads collected from an UAV. The dataset consists of 1300 images wth sorghum head annotations. You can find further information about the datasets for Training phase and Final test phase in the "Participate" tab under the heading "Get Data". The datasets could be downloaded from  the "Participate" tab under the heading "Files". The training dataset contains both labelled images and  unlabelled images. Participants are encouraged to use algorithms from active learning, semi-supervised learning or unsupervised learning for utilizing the unlabelled images during training.</description></item><item><title>全国高校大数据应用创新大赛</title><link>https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/4</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>全国高校大数据应用创新大赛”（以下简称大赛）是由教育部高等学校计算机类专业教学指导委员会、中国工程院中国工程科技知识中心和联合国教科文组织国际工程科技知识中心联合主办，复旦大学计算机学院承办，面向全国高校在校学生的，年度性大数据学科竞赛。 通用赛道： <a href="https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/6">大数据技术技能赛</a>: 大赛提供的数据和自选数据建立并训练模型，使之能够预测给定地区、日期和前置气象条件下，未来7天的部分气象要素的变化情况; <a href="https://ai.futurelab.tv/contest_detail/5">大数据与人工智能创意赛</a>: 本次大赛气象大数据开放式命题赛道，提供过去5年若干城市的气象数据，参赛选手可自主运用和扩充数据，设计一个基于气象大数据的跨行业跨领域的应用解决方案。</description></item><item><title>安泰杯 —— 跨境电商智能算法大赛</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231718/introduction?spm=5176.12281949.1003.1.3a994c2axCiMpB</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>本次比赛给出若干日内来自成熟国家的部分用户的行为数据，以及来自待成熟国家的A部分用户的行为数据，以及待成熟国家的B部分用户的行为数据去除每个用户的最后一条购买数据，让参赛人预测B部分用户的最后一条行为数据。</description></item><item><title>遥感图像稀疏表征与智能分析竞赛</title><link>http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>本次大赛设置<a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/1">遥感图像场景分类</a>、 <a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/2">遥感图像目标检测</a>、 <a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/3">遥感图像语义分割</a>、 <a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/4">遥感图像变化检测</a>和 <a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/5">遥感卫星视频目标跟踪</a>五个竞赛单元，并在决赛中设置 <a href="http://rscup.bjxintong.com.cn/#/theme/6">基于华为昇腾AI处理器的遥感图像解译加分赛</a>。 组织方将提供面向各竞赛单元的大规模遥感图像精确标注数据集与标准规范的测试数据， 制定可量化的算法评测标准，通过初赛、决赛和复审答辩等多个阶段的评比， 遴选出优秀的遥感图像解译算法，决胜出优胜团队。</description></item><item><title>飯田産業 土地の販売価格の推定</title><link>https://signate.jp/competitions/162</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>「日本語をネイティブに話せる方」</description></item><item><title>Automatic Structure Segmentation for Radiotherapy Planning Challenge 2019</title><link>https://structseg2019.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of the challenge is to set up tasks for evaluating automatic algorithms on segmentation of organs-at-risk (OAR) and gross target volume (GTV) of tumors of two types of cancers, nasopharynx cancer and lung cancer, for radiation therapy planning. There are four tasks for evaluating the performance of the algorithms. Participants can choose to join all or either tasks according to their interests. Task 1: Organ-at-risk segmentation from head &amp; neck CT scans. Task 2: Gross Target Volume segmentation of nasopharynx cancer. Task 3: Organ-at-risk segmentation from chest CT scans. Task 4: Gross Target Volume segmentation of lung cancer.            </description></item><item><title>Digestive-System Pathological Detection and Segmentation Challenge 2019</title><link>https://digestpath2019.grand-challenge.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The goal of the challenge is to set up tasks for evaluating automatic algorithms on signet ring cell detection and colonoscopy tissue screening from digestive system pathological images. This will be the first challenge and first public dataset on signet ring cell detection and colonoscopy tissue screening. Releasing the large quantity of expert-level annotations on digestive-system pathological images will substantially advance the research on automatic pathological object detection and lesion segmentation. Task 1: Signet ring cell detection. Task 2: Colonoscopy tissue segmentation and classification. </description></item><item><title>Open Images 2019</title><link>https://storage.googleapis.com/openimages/web/challenge2019.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>This year’s <a href="https://g.co/dataset/openimages">Open Images V5</a> release enabled the second <a href="https://storage.googleapis.com/openimages/web/challenge2019.html">Open Images Challenge</a> to include the following 3 tracks: <a href="https://www.kaggle.com/c/open-images-2019-object-detection">Object detection</a> track for detecting bounding boxes around object instances, relaunched from 2018. <a href="https://www.kaggle.com/c/open-images-2019-visual-relationship">Visual relationship detection track</a> for detecting pairs of objects in particular relations, also relaunched from 2018. Instance segmentation track [Link to be provided when launched on July 1], brand new for 2019.</description></item><item><title>Fashion IQ Challenge</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23391</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Fashion IQ is a new dataset we contribute to the research community to facilitate research on natural language based interactive image retrieval</description></item><item><title>Multi-domain Task-Completion Dialog Challenge [DSTC 8]</title><link>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/project/multi-domain-task-completion-dialog-challenge/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>As part of the Eighth Dialog System Technology Challenge (<a href="https://sites.google.com/dstc.community/dstc8/home?authuser=0">DSTC8</a>), Microsoft Research and Tsinghua University are hosting a track intended to foster progress in two important aspects of dialog systems: dialog complexity and scaling to new domains. For this DSTC8 track, there are two tasks you can compete in (see below). The challenge runs from June 17, 2019 – October 6, 2019. Participants will build an <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23263">end-to-end multi-domain</a> dialog system for tourist information desk settings. Participants will develop <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/project/multi-domain-task-completion-dialog-challenge/">fast adaptation</a> methods for building a conversation model that generates appropriate domain-specific user responses to an incomplete dialog history.</description></item><item><title>Oil Radish Semantic Segmentation and Yield Estimation Challenges</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23386</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The challenges associated with the dataset are the Semantic Segmentation challenge and the Yield Estimation challenge. In the Semantic Segmentation challenge, participants must perform pixel-wise classifiction on a subset of the labelled images. In the Yield Estimation challenge, participants must estimate the oil radish yield of same subset of labelled images.</description></item></channel></rss>