<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Update Log at Fri, 15 Feb 2019 GMT+0800</description><item><title>津南数字制造算法挑战赛【赛场二】</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231703/introduction?spm=5176.12281949.0.0.21e376d869oWRl</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>2019津南数字制造算法挑战赛，赛场二以物流货物限制品监测为课题，要求选手针对给出的限制品种类，利用X光图像及标注数据，研究开发高效的计算机视觉算法，监测图像是否包含危险品及其大致位置。通过自动化监测包裹携带品算法，降低漏检风险及误报率，提升危险品管理效率。</description></item><item><title>GQA Real-World Visual Reasoning Challenge 2019</title><link>https://cs.stanford.edu/people/dorarad/gqa/challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>斯坦福新视觉问答(VQA)数据集：GQA真实世界视觉推理数据集 “GQA: a new dataset for compositional question answering over real-world images”Given an image and a natural language question about the image, the task is to provide an accurate natural language answer.</description></item><item><title>The Animal-AI Olympics</title><link>http://animalaiolympics.com/</link><category>AC</category><category>RL</category><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>基于Unity ML Agents Toolkit的动物认知-AI 挑战This competition pits our best AI approaches against the animal kingdom to determine if the great successes of AI are now ready to compete with the great successes of evolution at their own game.</description></item><item><title>The Natural Language Decathlon: A Multitask Challenge for NLP</title><link>http://decanlp.com</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>The Natural Language Decathlon is a multitask challenge that spans ten tasks: question answering (<b>SQuAD</b>), machine translation (<b>IWSLT</b>), summarization (<b>CNN/DM</b>), natural language inference (<b>MNLI</b>), sentiment analysis (<b>SST</b>), semantic role labeling(<b>QA‑SRL</b>), zero-shot relation extraction (<b>QA‑ZRE</b>), goal-oriented dialogue (<b>WOZ</b>), semantic parsing (<b>WikiSQL</b>), and commonsense reasoning (<b>MWSC</b>).</description></item></channel><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Update Log at Tue, 05 Feb 2019 GMT+0800</description><item><title>2018 SUMO Challenge</title><link>https://evalai.cloudcv.org/web/challenges/challenge-page/159</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>The Scene Understanding and Modeling (SUMO) Challenge encourages the development of algorithms for complete understanding of 3D indoor scenes from 360 degree RGB-D panoramas with the goal of enabling social AR and VR research and experiences. </description></item><item><title>Activities in Extended Videos Prize Challenge</title><link>https://actev.nist.gov/prizechallenge</link><category>AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>(NIST)视频扩展行为(ActEV)挑战The Activities in Extended Videos Prize Challenge (ActEV-PC) seeks to encourage the development of robust automatic activity detection algorithms for an extended video.</description></item><item><title>Visual Dialog Challenge 2019</title><link>https://visualqa.org/challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Given an image and a natural language question about the image, the task is to provide an accurate natural language answer.</description></item><item><title>2019 SIOP Machine Learning Competition</title><link>https://evalai.cloudcv.org/web/challenges/challenge-page/160</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>In this competition, you will use unstructured text data to predict self-report personality traits. The top 4 teams with the most accurate predictions (on the Private Leaderboard) will be asked to present at the 2019 SIOP Special Session in April, 2019.</description></item><item><title>Visual Dialog Challenge 2019</title><link>https://visualdialog.org/challenge/2019</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Visual Dialog is a novel task that requires an AI agent to hold a meaningful dialog with humans in natural, conversational language about visual content. Specifically, given an image, a dialog history (consisting of the image caption and a sequence of previous questions and answers), the agent has to answer a follow-up question in the dialog. To perform well on this task, the agent needs to ground the query not only in the visual content but also in the dialog history.</description></item><item><title>fastMRI Image Reconstruction</title><link>https://evalai.cloudcv.org/web/challenges/challenge-page/153</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>By creating accurate images from under-sampled data, AI image reconstruction could enable faster scanning times, providing an improved experience for patients and potentially making MRIs accessible to more people.</description></item><item><title>ModaNet Fashion Understanding Challenge</title><link>https://evalai.cloudcv.org/web/challenges/challenge-page/151</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>In this challenge, we evaluate model performance for three tasks, object detection, semantic segmentation and instance segmentation. You can participate all tasks or any one of them by choosing which results to be included in your submission.</description></item><item><title>Vision and Language Navigation</title><link>https://evalai.cloudcv.org/web/challenges/challenge-page/97</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>RL/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>The challenge requires an autonomous agent to follow a natural language navigation instruction to navigate to a goal location in a previously unseen real-world building.</description></item><item><title>VizWiz Challenge 2018</title><link>http://vizwiz.org/data/#challenge</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Our proposed challenge addresses the following two tasks for this dataset: (1) predict the answer to a visual question and (2) predict whether a visual question cannot be answered.</description></item></channel></rss>