<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 06/08/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>Science of Science 数据黑客松</title><link>https://www.biendata.com/competition/hackathon/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>科学论文虽然代表了人类对自然最前沿的理解，但大众却很难读懂论文。所以论文发表后，科研机构经常会发布研究新闻稿解释论文中的研究。本次比赛的任务是给定一篇科研新闻，找到这篇新闻描述的论文。 提交数据格式: 新闻数据测试集press_test.csv中的每篇新闻都是在报道论文测试集paper_test.csv中的一篇论文。对于每篇新闻，选手需要从paper_test.csv中选出三篇最相关的论文。参赛者需要在训练集上训练模型，并对新闻和论文的相关行进行预测，最终可以标注 Top 3 的匹配结果。注意：预测出的匹配论文之间存在顺序，按照预测得分，从大到小排序。 本次黑客松任务即挂靠这次会议。在4天的时间里，参赛选手需要通过平台提交预测结果。前三名选手将获得4万元奖金，并被邀请到会议上介绍获奖方法。</description></item><item><title>2019 年县域农业大脑AI挑战赛</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231717/introduction</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>本次大赛，我们选择了具有独特的地理环境、气候条件以及人文特色的贵州省兴仁市作为研究区域，聚焦当地的特色优势产业和支柱产业——薏仁米产业， 以薏仁米作物识别以及产量预测为比赛命题，要求选手开发算法模型，通过无人机航拍的地面影像，探索作物分类的精准算法，识别薏仁米、玉米、烤烟三大作物类型，提升作物识别的准确度，降低对人工实地勘察的依赖，提升农业资产盘点效率，并结合产量标注数据预测当年的薏仁米产量，提升农业精准管理能力。</description></item><item><title>首届中文NL2SQL挑战赛</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231716/introduction</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>首届中文NL2SQL挑战赛，使用金融以及通用领域的表格数据作为数据源，提供在此基础上标注的自然语言与SQL语句的匹配对，希望选手可以利用数据训练出可以准确转换自然语言到SQL的模型。</description></item><item><title>The 2nd Large-scale Video Object Segmentation Challenge</title><link>https://youtube-vos.org/challenge/2019/</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>As a continuous effort to push forward the research on video object segmentation tasks, we plan to host a second workshop with a challenge based on the YouTube-VOS dataset, targeting at more diversified problem settings, i.e., we plan to provide two challenge tracks in this workshop. <a href="https://youtube-vos.org/dataset/vos/">Track 1: Video Object Segmentation</a> <a href="https://youtube-vos.org/dataset/vis/">Track 2: Video Instance Segmentation</a></description></item><item><title>Challenge: Learning To Drive (L2D)</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23245</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/RF</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Challenge participants need to develop driving models that can drive most similar to the human driver that recorded the dataset.</description></item><item><title>Challenge: Learning To Drive (L2D)</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23245</link><category>PF</category><category>CV/RF</category><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Challenge participants need to develop driving models that can drive most similar to the human driver that recorded the dataset.</description></item><item><title>2019 EE331 - Colorization</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23046</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Our goal is to make colorization from input images. The normal images are composed of RGB values, but we can represent these images into LAB values. In here, L means lightness. We cannot know the color of the image without the A and B values.</description></item><item><title>PharmaCoNER: Pharmacological Substances, Compounds and proteins and Named Entity Recognition track</title><link>http://temu.bsc.es/pharmaconer/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>For this task we have prepared a manually classified collection of clinical case sections derived from Open access Spanish medical publications, named the Spanish Clinical Case Corpus (SPACCC). The corpus contains a total of 1000 clinical cases / 396,988 words. It is noteworthy to say that this kind of narrative shows properties of both, the biomedical and medical literature as well as clinical records. Track 1: NER offset and entity classification. Track 2: Concept indexing.</description></item><item><title>政府治理大数据应用算法大赛</title><link>http://campus.chinahr.com/pages/cetctwo/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>国内外全日制<b>在校</b>大学生（包括全日制本科、硕士、博士研究生等非2019届毕业生），热爱算法建模、热爱数据分析、热爱应用开发等均可参赛。 本轮赛事仅设1题: <b>政策公文中的语义搜索</b>(需要根据输入的问题，返回对应的政策内容，以及相应的公文名称和具体条例)</description></item><item><title>DeepFashion2 Challenge 2019</title><link>https://sites.google.com/view/cvcreative/deepfashion2?authuser=0</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>DeepFashion2 (<a href="https://github.com/switchablenorms/DeepFashion2">github</a>) is a comprehensive fashion dataset. It contains 491K diverse images of 13 popular clothing categories from both commercial shopping stores and consumers. It totally has 801K clothing clothing items, where each item in an image is labeled with scale, occlusion, zoom-in, viewpoint, category, style, bounding box, dense landmarks and per-pixel mask.There are also 873K Commercial-Consumer clothes pairs. The dataset is split into a training set (391K images), a validation set (34k images), and a test set (67k images). <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23095">Track 1 Clothes Landmark Estimation</a> <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/23098">Track 2 Clothes Retrieval</a></description></item><item><title>第三届"长风杯"大数据分析与挖掘竞赛</title><link>http://contest.cfdsj.cn/index/care</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>第三届“长风杯”大数据分析与挖掘竞赛是一场面向全国普通高等院校经济与管理类、信息技术类等专业在校大学生的全国性赛事。 长风大数据平台将向本次竞赛的参赛者免费开放物流、电商、交通、公共、贸易等多行业的海量数据资源；其他生产型/服务型企业所提供真实数据。</description></item><item><title>Challenges and Opportunities in Automated Coding of COntentious Political Events (Cope 2019) @Euro CSS 2019</title><link>https://emw.ku.edu.tr/?event=challenges-and-opportunities-in-automated-coding-of-contentious-political-events</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>We use English online news archives from India and China as data sources to create the training and test corpora. India and China are the source and the target countries respectively in our setting.</description></item><item><title>Predicting Molecular Properties</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/champs-scalar-coupling</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>Can you measure the magnetic interactions between a pair of atoms?</description></item><item><title>Alchemy Contest</title><link>https://alchemy.tencent.com</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The Tencent Quantum Lab has recently introduced a new molecular dataset, called Alchemy, to facilitate the development of new machine learning models useful for chemistry and materials science. The dataset lists 12 quantum mechanical properties of 130,000+ organic molecules comprising up to 12 heavy atoms (C, N, O, S, F and Cl), sampled from the <a href="http://gdb.unibe.ch/downloads/">GDBMedChem</a> database. These properties have been calculated using the open-source computational chemistry program Python-based Simulation of Chemistry Framework (<a href="https://github.com/pyscf/pyscf">PySCF</a>).</description></item><item><title>MicroNet Challenge @NeurIPS 2019</title><link>https://micronet-challenge.github.io/</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019</pubDate><description>The competition consists of three different tasks. Contestants are free to submit entries for one, two, or all three tasks. Contestants are allowed to enter up to three models for each task, but will be ranked according to their top entry in each task. Entries can only be trained on the training data for the task they are entered in. No pre-training, or use of auxiliary data is allowed. <a href="http://image-net.org/index">ImageNet Classification</a>: The de facto standard dataset for image classification. The dataset is composed of 1,281,167 training images and 50,000 development images. Entries are required to achieve 75% top-1 accuracy on the public test set. <a href="https://www.cs.toronto.edu/~kriz/cifar.html">CIFAR-100 Classification</a>: A widely popular image classification dataset of small images. The dataset is composed of 50,000 training images and 10,000 development images. Entries are required to achieve 80% top-1 accuracy on the test set. <a href="https://blog.einstein.ai/the-wikitext-long-term-dependency-language-modeling-dataset/">WikiText-103 Language Modeling</a>: A language modeling dataset that emphasizes long-term dependencies. Entries will perform the standard language modeling task, predicting the next token from the current one. The dataset is composed of 103 million training words, 217 thousand development words, and 245 thousand testing words. Entries should use the standard word-level vocabulary of 267,735 tokens. Entries are required to achieve a word-level perplexity below 35 on the test set.</description></item></channel></rss>