<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 02/28/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>Explorer Challenge: A $1million prize pool to find Australia’s next big mineral deposit</title><link>https://unearthed.solutions/u/competitions/explorer-challenge</link><category>PF</category><category>DM/CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Join a global challenge to test the limits of data science and geology and develop new ideas about mineral exploration. OZ Minerals, a modern mining company, is opening up >2TB of their own private data from their exploration project, Mount Woods. Can you use this data to predict the next mineral deposit in South Australia? The winning models will be tested in real life, the top predictions will be drilled in 2019.</description></item><item><title>首届中国心电智能大赛</title><link>http://mdi.ids.tsinghua.edu.cn/</link><category>AC</category><category>CV/SP</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>自2012年起，国家陆续出台政策推动健康医疗和大数据的融合发展，从“健康中国”战略到“两个一百年”奋斗目标，健康医疗大数据已成为国家战略的创新需要，是国家及民族复兴所需的核心技术及国之重器。在此背景下，由清华大学临床医学院和数据科学研究院以及多家重点医院联合主办的首届中国心电智能大赛应运而生并于2018年12月20日正式启动。此次大赛获得天津市卫健委和河北省卫健委领导高度重视。预计大赛总奖金将高达百万元。</description></item><item><title>2019 Future Food Challenge</title><link>https://tianchi.aliyun.com/competition/entrance/231705/introduction?spm=5176.12281949.0.0.7e9276d8mqVJ8x</link><category>PF</category><category>DM/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Use the training data set to develop an <b>unsupervised</b> algorithm which identifies news items in the test set relating to the same food safety incident and assigns the same Event-ID to such group. </description></item><item><title>SkelNetOn - CVPR 2019</title><link>http://ubee.enseeiht.fr/skelneton/challenge.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>We release our dataset in different formats to run a competition with our workshop. We provide a shape dataset with corresponding skeleton representations in three domains, as well as some complementary sources (pre/post processing, sampling, and data augmentation scripts). The challenge will be posed as extracting the skeleton from a given shape, as detailed below. Mission 1: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21685">Shape Pixels to Skeleton Pixels</a> Mission 2: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21697">Shape Points to Skeleton Points</a> Mission 3: <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21775">Parametric Skeletons</a></description></item><item><title>MolHack 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21716</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>Verify your residency of <b>Taiwan</b>! At the minimum, the MolHack challenge will require the participants to build and train a Conditional Generative DNN model that can generate new small molecules such that the newly generated small molecules have similar MACCS fingerprints as the target MACCS fingerprint upon which the generation of the molecules is conditioned.</description></item><item><title>2019语言与智能技术竞赛 Language and Intelligence Challenge</title><link>http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>本届比赛设立了三个任务： 1. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/read'>机器阅读理解任务 Machine Reading Comprehension</a>：让机器阅读文本然后回答和阅读内容相关的问题， 阅读理解旨在使机器具备理解自然语言的能力。 2. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/talk'>知识驱动对话 Knowledge-driven Dialogue</a>：知识驱动对话是一种人机对话任务，机器根据知识信息构建的图谱进行主动聊天， 旨在使机器具备模拟人类用语言进行信息传递的能力。 3. <a href='http://lic2019.ccf.org.cn/kg'>信息抽取任务 Information Extraction</a>：信息抽取是指从自然语言文本中抽取实体、属性、关系等信息， 旨在使机器具备从海量文本自动构建知识的能力。</description></item><item><title>国际大数据分析竞赛 IEEE ISI-World Cup 2019</title><link>http://www.linkx.ac.cn/#/competition</link><category>AC</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>本次比赛基于3500家上市公司全量信息，描述公司在财务、法务、股权、经营状况、舆论等方面的属性特征，共设计两个任务， 两个任务将单独进行排名。团队可以报名一个或两个任务。 We provide full size information for over 3,500 listed companies in this competition. Two missions are given, based on the companies' attributes in terms of finance, legal affairs, equity, business status, public opinion, etc. And they will be ranked separately. One participation team can registrate one mission or two. Mission 1: 企业投资价值评估 Company Investment Value Evaluation Mission 2: 法律诉讼类型预测 Company Investment Value Evaluation</description></item><item><title>eHealth-KD @IberLEF 2019</title><link>https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/21781</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019</pubDate><description>More details are available at: <a href='https://knowledge-learning.github.io/ehealthkd-2019/'>https://knowledge-learning.github.io/ehealthkd-2019</a></description></item></channel></rss>