<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Data Science Challenge / Competition</title><link>https://iphysresearch.github.io/DataSciComp</link><description>Latest update at 05/17/2019 (GMT+0800).</description><item><title>TinyMind人民币面值&amp;冠字号编码识别挑战赛</title><link>https://www.tinymind.cn/competitions/47</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019</pubDate><description>针对人民币纸币面额及编码识别技术的深入研究，TinyMind发起本期挑战赛，诚邀广大AI界大佬,疯狂炫技，踊跃报名。 第一阶段：热身赛—— ⼈⺠币⾯值识别 第二阶段：正式赛——人民币冠字号编码识别</description></item><item><title>2019中国‘法研杯’司法人工智能挑战赛（CAIL2019）</title><link>http://cail.cipsc.org.cn</link><category>AC</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019</pubDate><description>本次挑战赛聚焦在<b>法律要素抽取</b>、<b>法律阅读理解</b>、<b>相似案例匹配</b>三个真实场景的任务，提供海量的已标注的法律文书数据，旨在为研究者提供学术交流平台，推动语言理解和人工智能领域技术在法律领域的应用，促进法律人工智能事业的发展。今年预计于10月在北京举办颁奖会和技术研讨会。诚邀学术界和工业界的研究者和开发者积极参与，比赛中发现的重大基础性问题，在国家自然科学基金专项资金中将予以重点考虑！</description></item><item><title>2019世界机器人大赛—BCI脑控机器人大赛 暨 第三届中国脑机接口比赛</title><link>http://www.worldrobotconference.com/html/jiqirendasai/saishi/2018/0314/290.html</link><category>PF</category><category>RL</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>脑-机接口（BCI）是指通过对神经系统电活动和特征信号的收集、识别及转化，使人脑发出的指令能够直接传递给指定的机器终端，从而使人对机器人的控制和操作更为高效便捷，该项技术在人与机器人的交流沟通领域有着重大创新意义和使用价值，其已广泛应用于助残康复、灾害救援、娱乐体验等多个领域，并在改善残疾人生活质量中做出了巨大贡献。</description></item><item><title>Game of Deep Learning: Computer Vision Hackathon</title><link>https://datahack.analyticsvidhya.com/contest/game-of-deep-learning/</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Do you feel passionate about solving problems through deep learning? Do you aspire to take data science to millions of people out there? Can the leader in you make people follow data science out of sheer passion? If the answer to all the questions is yes – look no more. Analytics Vidhya is looking for evangelists who can carry and deliver their baton to the world.</description></item><item><title>Learning to Run a Power Network (L2RPN 2019)</title><link>https://l2rpn.chalearn.org</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>RL</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>The challenge is based on an environment (and not solely a dataset) in which an agent can learn by interactions. </description></item><item><title>Data Science for Good: City of Los Angeles</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/data-science-for-good-city-of-los-angeles</link><category>PF</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Help the City of Los Angeles to structure and analyze its job descriptions. The goal is to convert a folder full of plain-text job postings into a single structured CSV file and then to use this data to: (1) identify language that can negatively bias the pool of applicants; (2) improve the diversity and quality of the applicant pool; and/or (3) make it easier to determine which promotions are available to employees in each job class.</description></item><item><title>SMP 2019 ETST 第二届文本溯源技术评测</title><link>https://www.biendata.com/competition/smpetst2019/</link><category>PF</category><category>NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>SMP 2019文本溯源评测由中国中文信息学会社会媒体处理专业委员会主办，黑龙江工程学院承办。本次技术评测以科研立项或成果创新型审查为应用背景，文本溯源的目标是判断一个文本的内容是否复制或改编于另外一个或者多个文本。文本溯源技术在学术诚信检测、搜索引擎优化等领域有广泛应用。</description></item><item><title>WIDER Face &amp; Person Challenge 2019</title><link>http://wider-challenge.org/2019.html</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Following the success of the <a href="http://wider-challenge.org/2018.html">First WIDER Challenge Workshop</a>, we organize a new round of challenge in conjunction with <a href="http://iccv2019.thecvf.com">ICCV 2019</a>. The challenge centers around the problem of precise localization of human faces and bodies, and accurate association of identities. It comprises of four tracks: <a href="http://wider-challenge.org/comingsoon.html">WIDER Face Detection</a>, aims at soliciting new approaches to advance the state-of- the-art in face detection. <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/22852">WIDER Pedestrian Detection</a>, has the goal of gathering effective and efficient approaches to address the problem of pedestrian detection in unconstrained environments. <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/22833">WIDER Cast Search by Portrait</a>, presents an exciting challenge of searching cast across hundreds of movies. <a href="https://competitions.codalab.org/competitions/22864">WIDER Person Search by Language</a>, aims to seek new approaches to search person by natural language.</description></item><item><title>Northeastern SMILE Lab - Recognizing Faces in the Wild</title><link>https://www.kaggle.com/c/recognizing-faces-in-the-wild/overview/description</link><category>PF</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Can you determine if two individuals are related?</description></item><item><title>ARIEL Data Challenge Series 2019</title><link>https://ariel-datachallenge.azurewebsites.net</link><category>AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>ARIEL, a mission to make the first large-scale survey of exoplanet atmospheres, has launched a global competition series to find innovative solutions for the interpretation and analysis of exoplanet data. You can find our press release <a href="https://arieldata.blob.core.windows.net/static/ariel_ml_datachallenge_press.pdf">here</a>. <a href="https://ariel-datachallenge.azurewebsites.net/ML">The first ARIEL Data Challenge</a> invites professional and amateur data scientists around the world to use Machine Learning (ML) to remove noise from exoplanet observations caused by starspots and by instrumentation. <a href="https://ariel-datachallenge.azurewebsites.net/retrieval">A second ARIEL Data Challenge</a> that focuses on the retrieval of spectra from simulations of cloudy and cloud-free super-Earth and hot-Jupiter data was also launched today. <a href="https://ariel-datachallenge.azurewebsites.net/#">A further data analysis challenge</a> to create pipelines for faster, more effective processing of the raw data gathered by the mission will be launched in June.</description></item><item><title>Graph Golf: The Order/degree Problem Competition</title><link>http://research.nii.ac.jp/graphgolf/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>DM/CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description><b>Find a graph that has smallest diameter &amp; average shortest path length given an order and a degree.</b> Graph Golf is an international competition of the order/degree problem since 2015. It is conducted with the goal of making a catalog of smallest-diameter graphs for every order/degree pair. Anyone in the world can take part in the competition by submitting a graph. Outstanding authors are awarded in CANDAR 2019, an international conference held in Nagasaki, Japan, in November 2019.</description></item><item><title>Propensity to Fund Mortgages</title><link>https://www.crowdanalytix.com/contests/propensity-to-fund-mortgages</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>DM</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Develop a model to predict, given mortgage application information, whether the mortgage will be funded or not. To predict whether a mortgage will be funded using only this application data, certain leading factors driving the loan’s ultimate status will be identified. Solvers will discover the specific aspects of the dataset that have the greatest impact, and build a model based on this information.</description></item><item><title>Identify Characters from Product Images</title><link>https://www.crowdanalytix.com/contests/identify-characters-from-product-images</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>Identify the characters from product image from a list of 42 possible values. While using machine learning to perform image recognition is currently one of the most popular use cases, in some cases, the existing large-scale models are too broad to be effective for specific business use cases. In this contest we will use a data driven approach to identify the “characters” in an image (product images). </description></item><item><title>nuScenes detection challenge</title><link>https://www.nuscenes.org/</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>The nuScenes dataset is a large-scale autonomous driving dataset.</description></item><item><title>ActivityNet-Entities Object Localization Task</title><link>https://github.com/facebookresearch/ActivityNet-Entities</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>ActivityNet-Entities, is based on the video description dataset ActivityNet Captions and augments it with 158k bounding box annotations, each grounding a noun phrase (NP). Here we release the complete set of NP-based annotations as well as the pre-processed object-based annotations. please see our dataset <a href="https://github.com/facebookresearch/ActivityNet-Entities">repo</a>, code <a href="https://github.com/facebookresearch/grounded-video-description">repo</a>, and CVPR 2019 oral <a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/1812.06587.pdf">paper</a>.</description></item><item><title>YouCook2 Dense Video Captioning</title><link>http://youcook2.eecs.umich.edu</link><category>PF/AC</category><category>CV/NLP</category><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019</pubDate><description>YouCook2 is currently suitable for video-language research, weakly-supervised activity and object recognition in video, common object and action discovery across videos and procedure learning.</description></item></channel></rss>